&gt;&gt; Hello, everyone.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
My name is John Blackwell, and
我是 John Blackwell
I'm an engineer on the Core
我是 Core Motion 框架
Motion framework.
的一名工程师
Today, we're going to be talking
今天 我们要讲一讲
about creating immersive
通过 Core Motion 框架
applications with the Core
来创建沉浸式
Motion framework; and we're also
应用软件 我们还会
going to discuss a number of
在过程中讨论一些
best practices along the way.
最佳实践的例子
So today, we're going to be
那么今天 我们将要
covering a number of things.
涉及到一系列话题
The first is a brief overview of
第一就是一个简单的概况
what Core Motion provides.
了解 Core Motion 可以提供什么
Next, we're going to talk about
接下来 我们会讲一下
authorization, a frequent pain
授权 这对于
point for many of our
我们的很多开发人员来说
developers.
是一个经常出现的痛点
Then, we're going to look at
然后 我们要看一下
some new additions to Historic
有关 Historic Accelerometer
Accelerometer; and then, we're
的一些新版本 再之后我们
going to dig into DeviceMotion,
要看一下 DeviceMotion
the sensor fusion that we
也就我们在 Core Motion
provide in Core Motion.
中提供的一个传感器混合体
And finally, we're going to look
最后 我们要看一下
at Badger with Attitude, a game
Badger with Attitude 它是一款游戏
where we'll take some of the
其中我们采用了一些
concepts that we've talked about
之前在 DeviceMotion 提到过的
in DeviceMotion and put them
概念 并且将它们付诸
into practice.
实际应用中
And with that, let's take a
那么好了 我们先
closer look at the Core Motion
仔细了解一下 Core Motion
framework.
框架
The Core Motion framework
Core Motion 框架
provides access to the
提供访问
accelerometer, the gyroscope,
accelerometer gyroscope
the magnetometer and the
magnetometer 以及
altimeter; and through the
altimeter 的途径 并且通过这一
framework, you can access raw
框架 你可以获取
forms of the sensor data, as
传感器数据的原始形式
well as process forms and use
以及处理过的形式 并且
these in your applications.
在你的应用软件中使用它们
Now, there are a number of
现在 有一些
interfaces available through
接口可以通过 Core Motion
Core Motion.
获取
The first is CMMotionManager,
第一个就是 CMMotionManager
which provides access to the raw
它帮助获取原始
sensor data, as well as the
传感器数据 以及
sensor fusion in the form of
DeviceMotion 形式的传感器
DeviceMotion.
混合体
CMAltimeter provides access to
CMAltimeter 帮助
relative altitude updates for
获取设备的相关高度
the device.
更新
CMPedometer provides access to
CMPedometer 帮助获取
step counts as step-related
步数 以作为步数相关
information, as well as
信息 以及
work-out, pause and resume
锻炼 暂停 和恢复
events.
活动
MotionActivityManager provides
MotionActivityManager 帮助
access to the activity context
获取设备的活动
of the device; for example,
情境 例如
walking, running or automotive,
走路 跑步 或坐车
etc. And CMSensorRecorder
CMSensorRecorder
provides access to historic
帮助获取
accelerometer data.
accelerometer 的历史数据
So that's a brief overview of
所以这就是一个概况
what the Core Motion framework
帮助我们了解 Core Motion 框架
provides.
提供什么
Next, let's take a closer look
接下来 我们来仔细看一下
at authorization.
授权
So of the APIs that I just
所以在我刚刚
mentioned, these following four
提到的 API 中 以下四种
are sensitive due to the nature
都非常敏感 这是由于
of the private information that
所显示的用户私人信息的本质所导致的
So to handle this, we have a
为了处理此事 我们会有一个
prompt that appears the first
提示符 在你第一次
time you invoke one of the
唤醒某一个 灵敏的 API 时
sensitive APIs.
它就会出现
Keep in mind that the first time
记住是当你第一次
you invoke the sensitive APIs, a
唤醒灵敏的 API 时 那个
prompt will appear for users;
提示符会出现在用户面前
but after that first time, your
但是第一次之后 你的
users will need to go into
用户就需要到
Settings to change the
“设置”来改变
authorization state for your
你应用软件的授权
applications.
状态
Now, let's take a look at what
现在 我们来看一看
it looks like the first time you
当你第一次
call one of these APIs.
调用这些 API 中的一个时是怎么样的
At this point, your users will
这时候 你的用户将
need to decide if they want to
决定他们是否想要
grant access to the Motion
允许访问 Motion
Fitness data; or deny access.
Fitness 数据 或者拒绝访问
And as a developer, you're going
作为开发人员 你会
to want to handle the case where
想要处理用户拒绝访问
they deny access.
这一问题
Now, in the past, we've asked
在过去 我们要求你
you to do something like this
做这样的事
where you call any of our APIs
你需要调用我们灵敏的
that are sensitive.
API
In this case we're calling
在这个例子中 我们正在调用
queryPedometerData; and then you
queryPedometerData 然后你
ignore the result that you get
无视从
back from the API and only look
API 获得的结果 只关注
at the error code.
错误代码
And if the error code is not
如果代码错误是因为
authorized, at this point, you
没有授权 这时
know your application's been
你就可以知道你的应用软件
denied access to that motion and
被拒绝访问动态和
fitness data.
健康数据
Now, we realize that this is
现在 我们意识到这种做法
less than ideal.
还不够理想
You need to jump through hoops
你需要跳过一环一环
to get access to your
来获得你的
authorization state, and once
授权状态 一旦
you get it, you can't tell
你得到了 你就无法知道
exactly why your app has been
为什么你的 App
denied access.
被拒绝访问
And that's why this year, we're
这就是为什么今年我们
providing an Authorization
提供了一个授权
Status API.
地位 API
This API is available in the
这个 API 在
same four classes that I
之前我提到的四类中
mentioned before, and it's
都可用 而且它也在
available on iOS and watchOS.
iOS 系统和 watchOS 系统上可用
Let's take a closer look at the
让我们进一步看一下
CMAuthorizationStatus value that
CMAuthorizationStatus 值
you'll get back from this API.
你将会从 API 得到它
The first state, notDetermined,
第一个状态是“notDetermined”
represents the state before the
它代表着
user has been asked about
用户还没有被问及
authorization in your
你应用软件的有关
application.
授权
Restricted represents the state
“Restricted”表示
where the user is unable to
用户无法
change the authorization state
为你的应该改变
for your application
授权状态
specifically; and this can
更确切地说
happen when motion and fitness
当动态和健康
is disabled in privacy.
在隐私中被禁用时会出现这样的状态
The next state -- denied --
下一个状态是“denied”
means what it sounds like.
就是指拒绝
Your application's been
你的应用软件
specifically denied access by
很明确地被用户
the users.
拒绝访问
And authorized means your app is
而“authorized”代表你的 App
ready to access the user's
已经被允许访问用户的
motion and fitness data.
动态和健康数据
Now, let's come back to the
现在 我们回过来看一下
authorization check that we were
我们之前正在看的
looking at before.
授权确认
One of the first best practices
第一批最佳实践中有一项
that I want to talk about is
我想要讲一讲
making sure that you check for
那就是确保你检查了
the availability of a given API
所给 API 的可用性
first before you ask for the
在你请求
authorization status.
授权地位之前
In this case, we're asking for a
在这个例子中 我们正在请求
StepCountingAvailable.
StepCountingAvailable
And the next thing that you're
接下来你
going to want to do is query for
想要做的就是请求
the authorization status.
授权地位
And at this point, it's up to
这个时候 是由
you as a developer to decide how
你 作为一个开发人员 来决定
you want to handle the
想要如何处理
authorization that you get back
从框架中拿回的
from the framework.
授权
You now have a simple mechanism
现在你有一个简单的机制
for doing this on both iOS and
可以来做这件事 无论是在 iOS 系统上还是在
watchOS.
watchOS 系统上
I encourage you to consider how
我鼓励你们考虑一下如何
you can use the authorization
使用授权
status app -- authorization
地位 App 也就是你应用软件中的
status API in your applications
授权地位 API
-- and you should definitely use
而且你应该
it.
使用它
Next, we're going to talk about
接下来 我们要讲一讲
Historical Accelerometer.
Historical Accelerometer
known as CMSensorRecorder,
也叫作 CMSensorRecorder
provide 50 hertz accelerometer
可以提供 50 赫兹的 accelerometer
data; and we can record this for
数据 而且我们可以
your applications while your
为你的应用软件记录这一数据 当你的
apps are in the background.
App 在后台运行时
You can request up to 36 hours
你可以请求最多 36 小时
of accelerometer data, and this
的 accelerometer 数据 这些
data will be stored on your
会被以你的名义
behalf for up to three days.
最多储存 3 天
Now, Historical Accelerometer is
现在 Historical Accelerometer
currently available on Apple
在 Apple Watch
Watch, and today, I'm excited to
可用 我很激动
announce that it's now available
地宣布它现在
on iPhone 7 and 7 Plus.
也在 iPhone 7 和 7 Plus 上可用
This opens up a whole new set of
这为你的应用软件开拓了
use cases for your applications,
全新的用例
and to get you thinking about
并且让你思考
how you can use Historical
要如何在 iPhone 上使用 Historical
Accelerometer on iPhone, let's
Accelerometer 让我们
walk through one sample
现在来看一个
application now.
简单的应用软件
So let's say you're a big
让我们假设你是一个
automotive enthusiast, and you
汽车狂粉
want to build an application to
你想要构建一款应用软件
enable you to track your car's
帮助你在很长的一段时间内
performance over a long-track
追踪汽车的
day.
性能
How would we go about building
那么我们要怎么样来构建
this?
它呢
Well, the first thing that we
好吧 首先我们
want to figure out is when the
想要弄清楚用户
user is driving, and for that,
何时驾驶 为此
we can use Motion Activity.
我们可以使用 Motion Activity
Motion Activity provides an
Motion Activity 提供一个
automotive state, and we can use
汽车的状态 我们可以用
this to determine the periods in
它来判断何时
which the user is driving.
用户在驾驶
Now, I want to take a brief
现在 我想要简单花
minute to talk about the
几分钟讲一讲
automotive detection.
汽车检测
In iOS 11, the automotive
在 iOS 11 系统中 汽车
detection has received special
检测这一块得到了格外的
attention to ensure
关注 以此来确保
best-in-class performance.
最佳的效果
This automotive state in Motion
在 Motion Activity 中的
Activity is the same state
汽车状态也
that's being used to power Do
被用来控制 Do
Not Disturb While Driving; and
Not Disturb While Driving 这一项功能
it's also available for you to
它也可以在你的应用软件中
use in your applications.
被使用
If, say, you wanted to
比如你想要
personalize your application's
在你的用户驾驶时
UI while the user is driving.
对应用软件的 UI 进行个性化设置
Now, coming back to our
现在 回到我们的
automotive performance tracking
汽车性能追踪
application, the next thing we
应用软件 我们下一步
want to do, is we want to gather
想要做的事 收集
the accelerometer data.
accelerometer 数据
And for that, we can use
对此 我们可以使用
SensorRecorder.
SensorRecorder
We can gather the accelerometer
我们可以收集
data for the periods in which
用户在驾驶期间的
the user is driving, and
accelerometer 数据 并且
translate that into metrics for
为用户将数据转换成公制
the user, such as how many Gs
的 例如
they were pulling through a
汽车在转弯时的
turn, or maximum lateral Gs or
G 值 或者是最大横向或
longitudinal Gs.
纵向加 G 值
Now, there are many different
现在 你可以考虑通过很多不同的
ways you could consider building
方式来构建
this kind of application, but by
这种应用软件 但是通过
using the Motion APIs, you can
使用 Motion APIs 你可以
provide your users with a
为你的用户提供一个
low-power, all-day experience.
低功耗 全天候的体验
Now, there are a number of best
现在请大家通过
practices to keep in mind with
Historical Accelerometer 记住一些
Historical Accelerometer.
最佳实践
The first is that you want to
首先 你会想要
choose the minimum duration that
为你的应用软件选择
makes sense for your
合理的最低持续
applications.
时间
So for automotive performance
所以对于汽车性能
tracking application, we may not
追踪应用软件而言 我们也许不
need the full 36 hours of data
需要全程 36 小时的数据
-- something more like 8 to 12
像 8 到 12
hours would make more sense.
小时更合理
And the next best practice to
接下来的最佳实践就是
keep in mind is to consider
要记得考虑
decimating or dropping samples
大批销毁或是减少样本
if you don't need the full 50
如果你不需要全部的 50
hertz accelerometer data.
赫兹 accelerometer 数据的话
These two suggestions, these two
这两条建议 这两项
best practices, will reduce the
最佳实践会减少
amount of processing that your
你的应用软件需要进行的
application is doing, and in
处理量 进而
turn, save the user's battery
也可以节省用户电池的
life.
寿命
Now, I encourage you to consider
现在我鼓励你想一想
how you can use Historical
你要如何在 iPhone上使用
Accelerometer on iPhone.
Historical Accelerometer
Next, let's talk about
下面我们来讲一下
DeviceMotion.
DeviceMotion
DeviceMotion is the name for the
DeviceMotion 是指
sensor fusion algorithm that we
传感器混合体算法 我们
provide in the Core Motion
将它提供在 Core Motion
framework.
框架中
Now, there are a number of
现在我们还在
things that go into
DeviceMotion 中
DeviceMotion.
新加了一些内容
The first sensor that we use in
我们在 DeviceMotion 中使用的第一个传感器
DeviceMotion is the
是
accelerometer, and the
accelerometer
accelerometer enables us to
通过 accelerometer 我们可以
measure the accelerations
测量用户
imparted by the user, as well as
传递的加速度 以及
the acceleration imparted by
重力
gravity.
加速度
The gyroscope enables us to
gyroscope 帮助我们
precisely measure the rotation
准确测量
rate of the device.
设备的转动率
And the magnetometer allows us
而 magnetometer 则帮助我们
to measure local fields around
测量设备周围的局部域
the device as well as the
以及
Earth's magnetic field.
地球磁场
Now, when dealing with the raw
当我们要处理原始
sensors, there's a number of
传感器时 需要记住
challenges to keep in mind.
一些我们面临的挑战
With the accelerometer, it can
使用 accelerometer
be difficult to distinguish from
我们很难区分
the accelerations imparted by
用户的
the user; and from those
加速度
imparted by the force of
和重力加速度
With the gyroscope, we can have
使用 gyroscope 我们可能
bias in the measurements over
对时间的测量会产生
time, and with the magnetometer,
偏差 使用 magnetometer
it can be difficult to
我们很难
distinguish between the local
区分局部域
fields and the Earth's magnetic
和地球磁场
And this is where DeviceMotion
这就是为什么我们引入了
comes in.
DeviceMotion
DeviceMotion provides 3D
DeviceMotion 可以提供 3D
attitude tracking while the
追踪
device is undergoing free-space
当设备正在经历自由空间
motion.
动态
And it does this by fusing
它通过合并
together all of the sensors to
所有的传感器
relay the advantages of each,
重新组织每一个的优点
while minimizing the
同时将缺点
disadvantages.
最小化
And as a developer, what this
对于开发人员来说
really means is it enables you
这意味着你
to focus on how you want to use
专注于自己想要如何使用
the motion data rather than the
动态数据 而不是
mechanics of trying to get the
纠结于如何最好地利用传感器这样的
best from the sensors.
技术性问题
Now, we've talked about
目前 我们已经在
DeviceMotion in a number of
之前的会议中讲过
previous sessions.
DeviceMotion
I encourage you to check them
我希望大家
out.
去看一下
We go into details about the
我们详细讲了
sensors and the DeviceMotion
传感器和 DeviceMotion
algorithms.
算法
But today, we're going to think
但是今天 我们要考虑的是
about how we can use certain
如何通过使用
aspects of DeviceMotion to
DeviceMotion 的某些部分来
create immersive applications
为你的用户创建
for your users.
沉浸式应用软件
So as a developer, when you're
作为一名开发人员 当你
first getting started with
第一次开始使用
DeviceMotion, the first thing
DeviceMotion 时 第一件
that you need to consider are
需要考虑的事情是
the reference frames.
参照系
The reference frames determine
参照系决定了
which sensors are used in the
会使用混合体中的哪一个
fusion, and how attitude is
传感器 以及如何
calculated for your
计算你应用软件的
applications.
空间方位
The first reference frame,
第一个参照系是
xArbitraryZVertical, fuses
xArbitraryZVertical
together the accelerometer and
它将 accelerometer 和
the gyroscope but does not use
gyroscope 合并 但没有使用
the magnetometer.
magnetometer
And the last three reference
其余三个参照系分别是
frames, xArbitraryCorrected,
xArbitraryCorrected
xMagneticNorth, and
xMagneticNorth 和
xTrueNorthZVertical, use all
xTrueNorthZVertical  同时使用
three sensors.
三种传感器
Now, let's talk about the first
现在 我们来讲一讲有关第一个
reference frame in more detail.
参照系的更多细节
Let's say you've got an awesome
假设你现在有一款很棒的
racing game where you're
竞速游戏
currently using touch controls
当前
to allow your users to steer in
你的用户可以通过触控
the game.
进行游戏
This is great, but we could
这很棒 但是通过使用动态
provide a more immersive
我们可以提供更加沉浸式的
experience using motion.
体验
What we want to do is we want to
我们希望我们
enable users to steer using
可以让用户
their device; so when they tilt
通过设别进行驾驶 那么当他们将
their car -- tilt their device
他们的车 他们的设备倾斜
to the left, the car will turn
到左边时 汽车就会
left.
左转
Now, as long as the device is
现在 只要设备是
relatively static, we can use
相对静止的 我们可以用
the accelerometer to estimate
accelerometer 来估算
the force of gravity; and once
重力 一旦
we have gravity, we can use that
我们得到了重力 就可以
to determine the tilt, or the
决定倾斜角度 或者是
angle offset from gravity.
重力抵消的角度
One thing to keep in mind,
但请记住一件事
though, is that if you were
如果你
using the accelerometer on its
让 accelerometer 自行运作的话
own, certain gestures can be
有些手势会
ambiguous.
很模糊
Tilting the device to the right
将装置向右倾斜
can look the same to the
对于 accelerometer 来说
accelerometer as sliding the
和将装置向左滑动
device to the left.
是一样
Now, one way you could consider
现在你可以考虑
dealing with this is by
处理这个问题 通过
averaging over the accelerometer
将 accelerometer 信号
signal.
平均化
In doing so, you would reduce
这样做的话 你可以减少
the short-term effects from the
来自用户的短期
user and leave only the
效应 只留下
long-term effects, such as the
长期效应 例如
force of gravity.
重力
However, in doing this, you
然而 这样做的话 你
would notice your application
也将注意到你的应用软件
would now respond more slowly.
的响应速度会更慢
And this is where DeviceMotion
这时候就需要 DeviceMotion
comes in.
发挥作用
DeviceMotion means that your
DeviceMotion 意味着你的
application doesn't need to
应用软件不需要
build up filtering logic to get
建立过滤逻辑就可以
great performance from sensors.
从传感器获取极大的性能
With the xArbitraryZVertical
xArbitraryZVertical
reference frame, this is the
参考系就是你
default reference frame that
应用软件的默认参考系
your application will receive if
如果
you don't explicitly specify one
你在开始
when you start DeviceMotion
DeviceMotion 更新时没有明确指明是哪个
updates.
参考系的话
And this reference frame is
这个参考系
great for use cases where you
对于使用来说是很棒的 当你
want to track the tip and the
想要追踪设备各角度的
tilt of the device.
倾斜的话
And for our use case in the
在游戏的用例
game, the accelerometer and the
中 accelerometer 和
gyroscope are going to fuse
gyroscope 合并使用
together to allow us to more
可以让我们更加
quickly and precisely track
快速且准确地追踪
gravity.
重力
And once we have gravity, we can
一旦有了重力 我们就可以
translate that into tilt for our
将它转换成倾斜角度设计到
game.
游戏中
Now, to walk through exactly how
现在我们来看看如何
to do this, my co-worker Ahmad
操作 我的同事 Ahmad
is going to come to the stage a
一会儿会来到讲台上
bit later and show us.
向我们展示
This reference frame is also
这个参考系对于
great for use cases where you
使用还很棒的一点在于当你
want to track gestures from the
想要追踪用户的
user.
手势时
I encourage you to check out our
我希望大家去看一下我们的
sample application, SwingWatch.
样本应用软件 SwingWatch
SwingWatch is an app that runs
SwingWatch 是一款在
on the watch that uses
手表上的 App
DeviceMotion to track when
它使用 DeviceMotion 进行追踪
you've made a forehand or a
当你在网球比赛中进行正手击球
backhand gesture during a tennis
或者反手击球时
Both the sample code and the
样本代码和
session are online, and I
会议都可以在网上找到
encourage you to check them out.
我鼓励大家去查看一下
So, let's say you've got another
那么 我们来假设你有另一款
game.
游戏
Let's say it's a shooter game
假定是一款射击游戏
where you allow the user to aim
你的用户可以
using virtual thumb-sticks.
通过虚拟的按钮开关进行瞄准
This is great, but we could
这很棒 但是通过动态
provide a more immersive
我们可以提供更加具有沉浸式的
experience using motion.
体验
And what we want to do is we
我们要做的是
want to determine where the user
判断用户在哪里
is pointing their device and
指向设备
have that translate into aiming
并且将这一信息转化
in the game; and for that, we
成游戏中的瞄准 为此 我们
want to use attitude.
想要使用空间方位
Attitude provides the rotation
空间方位可以提供
from the reference frame, fixed
旋转角度率
when you first start
从在你第一次
DeviceMotion updates, to where
DeviceMotion 更新时就固定的参考系到
the user is currently holding
用户当前在 3D 空间中握着的
the device in 3D space.
设备
Now, one way you could consider
现在 我们可以考虑用来
getting attitude is by taking
获取空间方位的途径是
the integral of a raw gyroscope
取得整个原始参数
signal.
信号
Your sway would determine the
你的摇摆会决定
attitude.
空间方位
However, this method for
然而
determining attitude would drift
这一判断空间方位的方法
over time due to bias in the
会随时间产生偏离 这是由于
gyroscope, and that's where the
参数的偏差 这时就需要
xArbitraryCorrectedZVertical
xArbitraryCorrectedZVertical
reference frame comes in.
参考系的帮助了
This reference frame uses the
这一参考系通过使用
magnetometer to improve the
magnetometer 来改进
horizontal attitude estimation
我们提供的水平
that we provide; and as a
空间方位预测 作为一名
developer, what this reference
开发人员 这个参考
frame means to you is it
系意味着
provides reliable attitude
通过一个固定的中心参考
performance with a fixed center
向你提供可靠的空间方位
reference.
性能
So in the game, your users can
所以在游戏中 你的用户可以
move the device around and then
来回移动设备然后
come back to a known center
找到一个已知的中心
location.
位置
Now, there are many other ways
现在 通过使用这个参考系
you could consider using this
你还有许多其他的方式
reference frame.
可以考虑
Let's say you wanted to build a
假设你想要构建一款
360-degree photo and video
360 度的相片和视频
player application.
播放应用软件
Your users would be able to move
你的用户可以转动
their device around and then
他们的设备然后
bring it back towards the center
回到追准一个中心的状态
-- towards the dock overlooking
这里即对准湖上的
the lake.
码头
Now, another way you could
另外一个你可以
consider using this reference
考虑使用参考
frame is for something like a
系的是有关
virtual-reality real estate
虚拟现实的房地产的
application where you want to
应用软件 你会想
allow your users to look around
让你的用户可以
at different parts of a room
从不同角度环顾房间
just by moving their device.
而仅需移动他们的设备
Now, let's say you build this
假设现在你已经构建了这样的一款
application out, and your users
应用软件 你的用户
love it; but they want to get a
很喜欢它 但是他们想要
better sense of in which
更清楚地了解
direction the windows face, or
窗户的朝向 或者
in which direction they can
哪个方向
expect the sun to rise.
可以看到日出
And for that, we want a world
为此 我们想要一个“环境
reference.
参考”
Now, you could consider using
现在你可以考虑使用
the magnetometer for this.
magnetometer 来完成它
This would provide a world
它可以提供一个“环境
reference and enable your
参考”而且你的
applications to orient with
应用软件可以根据环境
respect to the world.
作出适应
However, using the raw
然而 使用原始
magnetometer, you would find the
magnetometer 你会发现
output susceptible to
输出容易被
disturbances.
打乱
Some of these are inherent to
有一些是
the device, and some of these
设备固有的 而有一些是
are external to the device.
设备外的
This is where the final two
这个时候就需要用到最后两个
reference frames come in.
参考系了
These reference frames use the
这两个参考系使用
magnetometer to orient the
magnetometer 根据环境
device with respect to the
适应设备
world, and these reference
这些参考
frames handle magnetic
系处理的是磁性
device-level effects; as well as
设备级别的效应
in challenging magnetometer
还可以挑战 magnetometer
situations, we can stabilize the
的状况 可以
output.
使输出变得稳定
Now, choosing between these two
那么 在这两个
reference frames is going to be
参考系中作何选择则是
based on the needs of your
根据你应用软件的
application.
需求
If you've already got data
如果你已经获得了
that's referencing true north --
有关真北的数据
for example, map data -- it
例如 地图数据
would make sense to use the
那么使用
xTrueNorthZVertical reference
xTrueNorthZVertical 参考
frame.
系就更合理
Now, how could we consider using
那么我们要如何考虑使用
these reference frames?
这些参考系呢
Well, one example is things like
其中一个例子是
stargazing applications, where
观星指南应用软件
you want to allow your users to
你希望你的用户可以通过
point their device at a star in
将设备对准
the sky and identify it.
天空中的星星来进行识别
Another way you could
另外你还可以
considering using these
考虑将这些
reference frames are for things
参考系
like augmented reality
运用到增强现实
applications where you want to
的应用软件中去 在这类的应用软件中你需要
fuse the camera data with a
结合相机数据和
world reference.
环境参考
And for that, we encourage you
为此 我们会建议你
to check out ARKit.
查看 ARKit
ARKit's session follows
ARKit 会议将
immediately after this one.
紧随本次会议举行
Now, let's come back to our
现在 我们再回到
virtual-reality real estate
虚拟现实的房地产
application.
应用软件上来
Let's say you built the
假设你已经构建了一款
application out, and your users
应用软件 你的用户也很
love it, but you want to provide
喜欢它 但是你想要提供
them with more features.
更多的功能
Let's say you want to put
假设你想要
landmarks on the horizon in the
根据现实的位置
direction that they actually
在水平面上添加
are.
地标
How would we go about doing
我们要怎么
this?
做呢
Well, what we want is heading.
我们需要的是指向标
Heading gives us the direction
指向标为我们提供
the device is pointing with
设备所指的方向
respect to north.
这是相对于正北而言的
So when the device is pointing
所以当设备指着
straight towards north, heading
正北时 指向标
would return 0 degrees and as
会回到 0 度
the user rotates their device
当用户旋转他们的设备
around, the heading angle would
指向标的角度也会随之
update.
改变
Now, one way you could consider
现在你要考虑的是
getting heading is by using
通过使用 CoreLocation
CoreLocation.
获得指向标
CoreLocation provides a start
CoreLocation 提供一个开始
updating heading API that you
更新指向标 API 然后你
could then use the heading from
使用那个指向标
and fuse that in with the data
并进行合并 通过
that you're already getting from
你已经从
DeviceMotion.
DeviceMotion 获取的数据
One thing to keep in mind,
但要记住
though, is that CoreLocation's
CoreLocation
heading can fuse course.
的指向标可能会合并路线
Course is the direction of
路线这里是指
travel for the device.
设备移动的反响
Now, this may make sense for
这对于
things like turn-by-turn
逐向
navigation applications, but for
导航应用软件也许是合理的 但是对于
things like augmented reality,
增强现实应用软件来说
this may make less sense.
就不那么合理了
I encourage you to check out
我希望你可以
CoreLocation's section on
听听周四的 CoreLocation 会议
Thursday for more details.
以获取更多细节
Now, another way you could
此外你可能还考虑
consider getting heading is by
通过我们提供在 DeviceMotion
calculating it from the attitude
中的空间方位估算
estimation that we provide in
来获得
DeviceMotion.
指向标
However, getting this right in
然而 要想在
all circumstances is
所有情况下把这件事做正确
non-trivial; and this is why
绝非容易的事 这也是为什么
this year, we're adding heading
今年我们在 DeviceMotion
as a first-class property in
中添加了指向标 并将它作为
DeviceMotion.
一项顶级的性能
Heading fuses together the
指向标将
accelerometer, the gyroscope and
accelerometer gyroscope 以及
most importantly, the
最重要的
magnetometer, to give us the
magnetometer 合并起来 利用正北方向
direction the device is pointing
为我们提供设备所指
with respect to north.
的方向
Keep in mind that heading is
记住 指向标
only available on iOS, where the
仅在 iOS 系统上提供 同时
magnetic field property is
磁场特性也是
available.
可用的
Now, let's take a closer look at
现在我们来仔细看一下
the API.
API
Heading is only valid for the
指向标仅对
xMagneticNorth and xTrueNorth
xMagneticNorth 和 xTrueNorth
reference frames.
参考系有效
For the other two reference
对以其他两个参考系
frames, you'll receive a
你会
negative value back from
从指向标收到一个负值
heading, and heading will give
指向标会
you from 0 to 359 degrees from
从你在你应用软件中
the X axis that you've chosen in
选择的 X 轴上 给你 0 到 359 度
your application, either
的数值范围 无论是
MagneticNorth or TrueNorth.
MagneticNorth 还是 TrueNorth
Now that we have heading, we
既然我们有了指向标 我们
could use that to overlay the
就可以用它来
Golden Gate Bridge on the
将金门大桥
horizon in the direction that it
放置在它
actually is.
实际的方位上了
Now, with DeviceMotion, there
现在 通过 DeviceMotion
are a number of best practices
我们有一些最佳实践
to keep in mind.
需要记住
The first is that you want to
首先 你要
make sure that you check for the
确保在开始更新之前
availability of a given
检查所给
reference frame before you start
参考系的
updates.
可用性
And to do that, you can use the
为此 你可以使用
availableAttitudeReference
availableAttitudeReference
Frame's API.
Frame 的 API
This will return you a
它会返回给你一个
CMAttitudeReferenceFrame bitmask
CMAttitudeReferenceFrame 位掩码
that you can then and, with the
然后你可以通过
reference frame that you are
相关的参考系
interested in, to determine
来确定
availability.
可用性
And the next thing to keep in
下一件要
mind is that the choice of
记住的是 选择
reference frame is key for your
参考系对于你的应用软件来说
applications.
很关键
This is going to determine how
这会决定
attitude is calculated in your
如何计算你应用软件的
applications, as well as which
空间方位 以及决定哪些
sensors go into the sensor
传感器会被
fusion.
合并
Now, we've talked about a number
现在 我们已经讲了一些
of things in DeviceMotion, but
有关 DeviceMotion 的事
let's get a little bit more
让我们来讲讲更加
practical.
实际的东西
Let's take some of the concepts
我们来讲讲
that we've talked about in
我们在 DeviceMotion 中讨论过的一些概念
DeviceMotion and put them into
然后通过一个游戏
practice using a game.
看看它们的实际应用
Badger with Attitude is a game
Badger with Attitude 是一款游戏
where we're going to apply
其中我们需要使用
DeviceMotion to translate into
DeviceMotion 为游戏
controls for the game, and for
转换控制
that, I'd like to invite my
为此 我会请我的
co-worker, Ahmad to the stage to
同事 Ahmad 到台上来
walk us through this.
跟大家讲一讲这个
[ Applause ]
[鼓掌]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, John.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 John
Hello, and welcome.
大家好 欢迎来到这里
Today, I'm going to be taking
今天我会讲一讲
some of those concepts that John
有关那些概念的问题 也就是 John
just talked about and help you
前面提到的
put them through a practical
通过一个实例帮大家加深
example.
了解
My name is Ahmad, and I'm an
我叫 Ahmad 我是
engineer on the Core Motion
Core Motion 团队的一名
team.
工程师
I'll be using the Badger app,
我将会使用 Badger 这个 App
which has been developed by our
它是由我们在 SceneKit
colleagues over at SceneKit.
的同事开发的
You may have seen this app in
你也许已经看到过它了
last year's session.
就在去年的会议上
In it, you play a cute little
在这款游戏里你需要操控一只很可爱的
badger called Bob.
小獾 他叫 Bob
He sits in a mining cart rolling
他坐在一个采矿车里 在
down some tracks, selecting gems
车轨上颠簸 一路上
and power-ups along the way.
挑选宝石和获取能量
So we're going to take this app
所以我们要来讲一讲这款 App
with existing swipe controls and
通过现存的滑动操作
use DeviceMotion to transform it
并使用 DeviceMotion 将其变成
to motion-based gestures.
基于动态的姿势
Here's what we've got in store
这是现在商店中可以为你
for you today: First, we're
提供的： 首先我们
going to talk about the existing
要讲讲现存的
controls and what we're trying
控制 以及我们正在努力
to accomplish.
完成的
Then we'll show you some of the
然后我们会向你展示
basics of using DeviceMotion.
关于使用 DeviceMotion 的一些基本的东西
And finally, the algorithms we
最后 我们用算法
use to detect those gestures.
来捕捉那些姿势
So the Badger app allows you to
在 Badger 这款 App 中
swipe your finger up across the
你可以在屏幕上滑动手指
screen to make the badger jump,
来使獾跳动
and if you swipe your finger
如果你下滑手指
down, the badger ducks and hides
獾会低头藏在
inside the card to avoid the
手推车里 以避开
obstacles.
障碍物
And swiping left or right will
向左右滑动可以
make the badger swing to reach
让獾通过摆动
out for those gems.
够到宝石
If you've worked on beautiful
如果你在这么美丽的
graphics like these, it's a
图案上进行操作
shame to have to hide them
仅仅将它们藏在
behind your finger while you
手指后面玩游戏的话
play the game.
就太可惜了
So let's use the phone as our
所以 这里我们就将手机作为
controller here and have the
控制器 让
user fully immersed in the
用户完全沉浸在
experience that we've built for
我们为他们构建的体验中
them.
那么首先 我们要检测
user has rotated the device
用户是否将设备
towards them to make the badger
转向自己来使獾
jump up.
跳跃
A slight bump in the device
轻微地向下晃动设备
downwards will make the badger
可以使獾
squat and hide in the cart.
蹲下藏到手推车里
And tilting the device left or
向左或向右倾斜设备
right will make the badger lean
会使獾相应地进行
either way.
倾斜
Now I want you to focus on those
现在我想让你关注在
couple of points and think about
这些点上
them when you're looking at the
当你之后在看着
sample code later, or thinking
样本代码时想一想它们 或者
about incorporating motion into
想一想如何将动态并进
your application.
你的应用软件
As John has mentioned earlier,
正如 John 已经提到的
Core Motion allows you to
通过 Core Motion 你可以
interact directly with the
直接和传感器进行
sensors.
互动
Let's take the accelerometer,
拿 accelerometer
for example.
来说
That input may look fine as long
只要用户是半静止的状态
as the user is semi-stationary,
那样的输入看上去还行
but if you start walking around
但是当你开始走动
or get on a bus, then you're
或者上一辆公交车 你就
going to have to account for
必须考虑
these additional accelerations.
这些额外的 加速度
So with DeviceMotion, we've
通过 DeviceMotion 我们已经
taken other sensors like the
用其他的传感器 比如
gyro and the magnetometer that
gyro 和 magnetometer 来
complement the accelerometer
对 accelerometer 进行了
really well, and we fuse those
很好的补充 我们
inputs for you so we can
为你合并这些输入 这样一来我们可以
minimize those environmental
将环境因素的影响
factors and let you focus on
最小化 让你专注在
capturing those motion controls
捕捉动态控制上
rather than how to process the
而不是如何处理
sensor input.
传感器的输入问题
The DeviceMotion APIs allow you
通过 DeviceMotion API 你可以
to query for samples in two
以两种不同的方式来质询
different ways, the push and the
样本 即“推”和
pull mechanisms.
“拉”这两种机制
Let's take a close look at those
让我们来仔细看一下这
two.
两个机制
The push mechanism is a great
“推”这一机制对于
way for you to detect a discrete
捕捉一定时间内
gesture across a small window of
的分离姿势是很
time.
有用的
In the SwingWatch app from last
在去年的 SwingWatch App 中
year's session, we used the push
我们使用了“推”
mechanism so that the framework
这个机制 因此框架
will push to us updates as they
会在固定的间隔内
are available at a fixed
向我们推一些更新 只要
interval.
有更新的话
Then we would capture those
然后我们会捕捉这些
updates and detect if the user
更新并且检测用户是否
swung their arm to perform a
摆动手臂来进行
backhand or a forehand.
反手击球或正手击球
This is what the API looks like.
这就是 API 的样子
You use the CMMotionManager's
你使用 CMMotionManager 的
start DeviceMotion updates
开始 DeviceMotion 更新
function; you provide a
功能 你提供一个
reference frame of interest,
相关的参考系
provide an operation cue for
提供一个操作线索 来使
your motionHandler to run on as
你的 motionHandler 尽快
soon as those samples are ready.
处理那些已有的样本
However, if you want to know
然而 如果你先要知道
what the current state of the
设备的当前状态
device is, then you want to use
那么你需要在这里使用
the pull mechanism here.
“拉”这个机制
As we'll show you later on in
正如我们之后会在
the Badger app for the tilt
Badger 这款 App 演示 对于倾斜
gesture, we want to make the
姿势 我们想要让
Badger lean at the same angle
獾的倾斜角度
that the phone is in.
和手机一样
So we ensure we provide the
因此我们要确保
responsive and smooth experience
为我们的图形应用软件提供
for our graphical application.
反应灵敏而流畅的体验
The API for the pull mechanism
“拉”机制的 API
is a bit simpler.
更简单
You call
你调用
startDeviceMotionUpdates, and
startDeviceMotionUpdates 然后
you provide the reference frame;
提供参考系
and whenever you're ready, you
只要你准备好了 你就
can pull for the latest
可以从框架中拉取最新的
DeviceMotion sample from the
DeviceMotion
framework.
样本
We'll be releasing the sample
我们还将发布样本
code for use, so you'll be able
代码以供使用 你之后
to take a look at it later, but
可以看一下 但是现在
let's focus on the Core Motion
让我们先来关注 Core Motion
parts for now.
的部分
So to get start with them for
那么让我们从它们开始
the Core Motion framework and
介绍 Core Motion 框架
then instantiate an instance of
然后举一个
the CMMotionManager.
CMMotionManager 的例子
Then we'll check if DeviceMotion
然后我们检查一下 DeviceMotion
updates are available on this
更新在这个平台是是否
platform.
可用
And if you recall from John's
如果你回忆刚才 John
talk, the tip and tilt gestures
讲的 我们
that we're interested in track
关注的
where gravity is in the device
关于追踪重力的倾斜姿势也在
frame.
设备框中
So we'll be using the
我们会使用
xArbitraryZVertical reference
xArbitraryZVertical 参考
frame, and we'll check if it's
系 我会还会检查它使用在
available on the platform.
平台上可用
You may have noticed I did not
你也许注意到了在这里我没有
check for the authorization
检查授权
here, and that's because I'm
这是因为我正在
using the MotionManager API,
使用 MotionManager API
which does not access sensitive
它并不访问敏感
data.
数据
For the rest of the talk, we'll
接下来的部分 我们会
assume the device is in the
假定设备属于
[inaudible] orientation, but in
最后一种定向 但是
the sample code, we'll show you
在样本代码中 我们会向你展示
how to detect and handle other
如何捕捉处理其他的
device orientations.
设备定向
For the first gesture, when
对于第一种姿势 当
rotating the device towards you
向自己旋转设备
makes the badger jump up, we
来使獾起跳时 我们
want to capture the magnitude of
想要捕捉
that rotation rate along the
手机水平轴的
horizontal axis of the phone.
旋转率数值
In this case, it's the Y-axis.
在这个例子中 也就是 Y 轴
So we'll be looking at the
那么我们还要看一下
rotation rate property from the
DeviceMotion 目标的
DeviceMotion object.
旋转率特性
And we chose that specifically
我们特别选择它
because we're not interested in
是因为我们与
the current angle the device is
设备当前的角度不相关
making, but rather a quick
与我们相关的是
change in that angle.
那个角度的快速改变
So if we use the rotation rate,
所以如果我们使用旋转率的话
we'll be able to detect a quick
我们就可以检测到快速的
pulse and make the badger jump
跳动 并且让獾相应地
accordingly.
进行跳跃
This is a gesture that we're
这是我们
detecting across a small period
在很短的一段时间要检测到的
of time, so we're going to be
姿势 因此我们要对它
using the push mechanism for it.
使用“推”机制
Let's see how that will look in
让我们来看看它
the code.
在代码里是什么样的
To start off, we'll set the
最开始 我们要将
update interval to 50 hertz.
更新间隔设为 50 赫兹
And you want to be careful when
你需要在设置的时候
you set that.
很小心
You want the samples to be
你希望样本
coming in fast enough so that
过来的足够快 这样的话
you can capture that gesture;
你就可以捕捉那个姿势
but not too fast that you're
但是也不要太快
increasing your computational
那样会提高对计算
and memory requirements.
和记忆的要求
Then we'll start DeviceMotion
然后我们开始
updates using the push
使用“推”机制进行 DeviceMotion 更新
mechanism, provide our
提供我们的
xArbitraryZVertical reference
xArbitraryZVertical 参考
frame, a queue, and I'm using a
系 一个“queue” 我正在这里
standard operation cue here, and
使用标准操作线索
finally, our motionHandler.
最后就是我们的 motionHandler
This is what our motionHandler
这就是我们的 motionHandler
will look like.
的样子
It will get called as soon as
只要样本准备好了
samples are ready.
就可以调动它
The first thing we'll do is
我们要做的第一件事就是
check for any errors and then
检查所有的错误
grab that rotation rate from the
从 DeviceMotion 目标获取旋转率
DeviceMotion object, and look at
然后看一下
the Y-component that we were
与我们相关的
interested in.
Y 轴分量
Then we store that in a buffer,
然后我们将它储存在缓冲存储器中
and I'm using the circular
我这里使用的是循环
buffer here, so as soon as the
缓冲 因此只要
samples are coming in, we'll
样本过来 我们就可以
accumulate more of them.
积累更多
Since we're using the SceneKit
由于我们为这个应用软件
renderer for this application, I
使用的是 SceneKit 渲染器
chose the renderer's
我选择渲染器的
updateAtTime function.
updateAtTime 功能
This will get called just before
在你渲染一个新的场景之前
you render a new scene, and this
它会被调用 这
is the ideal place for me to
对于我来说是一个理想的地方
check for the state of that
来检查缓存状态
buffer and then update the game.
然后更新游戏
And I'll leave it up to you to
我会让你们
find out where in the
自己去发现
application is the best place to
应用软件里的哪一个地方最适合
do that.
做那件事
And then I simply check if the
然后我只需要检查一下
mean of that buffer has crossed
那种缓存的方式是否跨过了
a certain threshold and make the
某一界点使得
badger jump.
獾可以跳跃
Keep in mind this threshold is
记住这个界点
tunable and adjustable to your
是可以根据你 App 的特殊需求
app's specific needs.
来进行转变和调整的
Next, we'll take a look at the
接下来我们要看一下
second control, where bumping
第二个控制 在第二个控制中当我们
the device downwards will make
向下晃动设备时
the badger duck.
獾会下蹲
For this one, we want to measure
对于这个控制 我们要测量的是
the user acceleration along the
用户顺着重力矢量的
gravity vector.
加速度
So we'll be looking at the user
所以我们要看用户的
acceleration property, and here
重力性能 这里
we chose that because even if
我们选择它是因为哪怕
the device is slightly tilted or
设备稍微倾斜或
rotated at an angle, the user
旋转一定角度 用户的
acceleration is going to still
加速度还是
look the same regardless of the
一样的 不管空间方位
attitude.
如何变化
So this is one of the gestures
因此这又是一个
again that we're detecting over
我们要在短时间内检测的
a window of time, so we'll use
动作 我们也会
the push mechanism as well.
使用“推”机制
Since we're already set up for
由于我们已经建立了
the push mechanism, we'll head
“推”机制 我们将会
back to our motionHandler, where
返回我们的 motionHandler
we were storing those rotation
在那里我们之前存储了那些
rates previously.
旋转率
But this time, we'll put out the
但是这次 我们要将
gravity property out of the
重力性能排除在
DeviceMotion object and the user
DeviceMotion 目标外 以及
acceleration as well.
用户的加速度
We compute the magnitude of that
我们计算
user acceleration along the
顺着重力矢量的用户加速度的值
gravity vector and store that in
将它存储在
a buffer.
一个缓冲器里
And once the mean of that buffer
一旦缓冲方式
crosses a certain threshold,
超过了某个界点
then we'll make the badger duck
我们就会让獾
down and hide in the cart.
蹲在并且藏在手推车里
So we've taken a look at two
所以我们来看一眼这两个
controls where we were
控制 我们通过在这两个控制
monitoring motion across a small
来监测一小段时间内的动态
window of time and we used the
我们还为此使用了
push mechanism for that.
“推”机制
Let's take a look at our final
让我们来看一下最后一个
control, where our requirements
控制 对于这个控制我们的要求
are slightly different.
稍有不同
For the tilt control, in the
对于倾斜控制来说
simple case where the device is
举个简单的例子 当设备被
held in a vertical position, you
垂直拿着时
can break down the gravity
你可以将重力
vector into its x-component and
矢量分割成 X 轴分量
its y-component; and by applying
和 Y 轴分量 通过运用
simple trigonometry, you can
简单的三角学原理
arrive at the tilt.
你可以达到倾斜
But since we want this gesture
但是由于我们希望这个姿势
to be slightly more flexible,
更加灵活
we're going to break gravity
我们要将重力分成
into its y-component; and its
Y 轴分量
component in the x-z plane of
以及在设备 X－Z 轴上的
the device.
分量
This will allow us to tilt the
这样一来
phone even if the device is
哪怕设备稍微旋转了一定角度 我们也可以
slightly rotated at an angle.
倾斜手机
What's different about this
这个控制的不同之处在于
control is that we want to know
我们想要知道
the current state of the device
设备的当前状态
and not a discrete motion that
而不是发生的
occurred.
分离动态
This will allow us to make the
这使我们可以让
badger lean at the same angle
獾根据设备的倾斜角度
the device is leaning in and
倾斜同样的角度
provide a very responsive
并且提供非常灵敏的
experience.
操作体验
And for those reasons, we'll be
基于那些原因 我们将
using the pull mechanism for
为此控制使用
this control.
“拉”机制
Since we're already set up for
由于我们已经建立了
framework is ready for us to
当我们要拉回
pull for samples at any point in
任何时间点的样本时
time.
框架都是准备好的
So we'll go back to our renderer
所以我们要回到我们的渲染器
function.
功能
If you recall, this is getting
回想一下 它会在
called just before you render a
你渲染一个新场景之前
new scene.
被调用
That makes it a perfect place
这使得它成为了
for me to pull for the latest
我拉回最新样本的最佳
sample, make a calculation, and
场所 也是计算和
then update the graphics.
更新图画的最佳场所
So we'll ask the MotionManager
所以我们会向 MotionManager
for the latest DeviceMotion
请求最新的 DeviceMotion
sample, grab the gravity
样本 不考虑
property out of it, compute the
重力性能 来计算出
vector and the x-z plane, and
矢量和 X-Z 轴的分量
arrive at the tilt as the atan
以达到倾斜 也就是
between that x-z-component and
X—Z 轴分量和
the y-component.
Y 轴分量的反正切函数
Don't forget to let the
不要忘记
framework know that you're no
让框架知道你和
longer interested in
DeviceMotion 更新不再相关了
DeviceMotion updates if they
不再相关了
were previously active.
如果它之前是有效的话
This is a great thing to do when
这一点很棒
your game is paused or has ended
当你的游戏暂停或结束时
to make sure you're not wasting
它可以确保你没有浪费
more battery than you need.
多余的电量
So here you see the results.
这里你可以看到一个结果
The user is able to play the
用户可以
game by tilting the device from
通过将设备倾斜到一边
side to side to make the badger
来使獾也以同样的方式倾斜
lean either way, and tipping the
向他们的方向倾斜
device towards them makes the
设备可以让
badger jump up, and finally, a
獾跳起来 最后
small push of the device
向下轻推设备
downwards will make the badger
可以使獾
squat and hide inside the cart.
下蹲并躲在手推车里
It's pretty cool, we've taken an
这很酷 我们已经
app with swipe controls and used
通过滑动控制和使用
DeviceMotion to replace them
DeviceMotion 来取代
with motion-based ones.
原本基于动态的控制
I'm excited to see how far you
我很激动地想要看到
can push the DeviceMotion APIs.
你们能将 DeviceMotion API 应用成什么样
[ Applause ]
[鼓掌]
So to wrap up some of the key
所以来总结一下
points that we talked about
我们今天讨论的几个关键点
today, we encourage you to look
我们希望你看一下
at the authorization API and
授权 API
check for your app's
并且检查一下你 App 的
authorization if you're using
授权 来看一下你使用的 API
one of the sensitive APIs.
是否灵敏
While you might have your use
你也许有
case for using the sensor data
直接使用传感数据的用例
directly, we encourage you to
我们还是希望你
look at the DeviceMotion APIs,
看一下 DeviceMotion API
because our sensor fusion
因为我们的传感器混合
algorithms handle the most
参数可以处理
common case.
绝大多数案例
It eliminates those
它可以排除那些
environmental factors so that
环境因素
you are able to focus on the
因此你可以专注在
motion controls of your user.
用户的动态控制上
The APIs provide you a smooth
API 为你提供了一个流畅
and consistent experience across
且连贯的体验
all our supported devices, and
在所有我们支持的设备上都是如此
we've made enhancements this
我们本次发布还做了一些改进
release to make sure that when
来确保
you query for those updates, you
当你询问更新时
do that in a very
可以通过一种
power-efficient manner.
低能耗的方式
Remember the two different ways
记住两种不同
to query for updates: Use the
询问更新的方式
push when you want to detect a
当你想要捕捉
gesture across a small window of
很短时间内的一个姿势时使用“推”
time, and use the pull when
当灵敏性很重要且你
want to know what the current
想要知道设备的
state of the device is.
当前状态时用“拉”
Here are a couple of the
还有一些会议
sessions that we think you might
我们觉得你们可能会
be interested in.
感兴趣
Please check them out, and if
请关注它们
you're interested in learning
如果你有兴趣
more about the Badger app, check
了解更多关于 Badger App 的内容
out last year's SceneKit
请查看去年的 SceneKit
session.
会议
If you follow this link, you'll
在这个链接中
be able to get at the sample
你可以获得样本
code and other Core Motion
代码 以及其他有关 Core Motion
documentation.
的文件
We thank you all for being here,
感谢大家今天的出席
and have a wonderful evening.
祝大家度过一个美好的夜晚